Well, look at that. We've finally made it.
Ugh, finally is right. It's always tough to find gentlemanly companionship on the road.
All right. I'm off to meet this genus person in administration. What are you doing the rest of the day?
I think I'll be joining you.
Oh, yeah? Are you interested in studying here?
No, but I am extremely interested in the student body.
Of course, yeah.
On the journey here, Alina Lise revealed to me that her promiscuity is due in large part to a curse.
If she doesn't get any for a little too long, her health will rapidly deteriorate.
Guess we should be on our way, then.
Thank you for waiting. I am Genus, the vice-principal here.
It's a pleasure to meet you. I'm Rudeus Greyrat.
And my name is Alina Lise Dragonroad. I'm a member of Rudeus' party.
I have to admit, I didn't think we would get to welcome you so soon.
Well, I was advised to come quickly.
Were you? Oh, yes. By Roxy, I suppose.
That's Ms. Roxy to you, asshole.
In any case, I take it you intend to enroll? What is it that you would like to accomplish here?
A number of things. I have some research I'd like to do. Magic's still to learn.
I just decided this was the right place to do it.
I'm glad to hear you answer honestly.
But now, if you wouldn't mind, I would ask your cooperation as we administer a little test.
What kind of test?
The grounds go on forever. Do you really have that many students enrolled here?
Yes, we cater to all. Unlike most magically-focused academies,
Runaway University offers programs in non-magical disciplines as well.
Really? Would those programs by any chance include a medical course that handles the study of mental illness?
I've never heard of a medical course in mental illness, but we do offer classes in healing, detoxification magic,
and we have a department for the study of curses.
Why do you inquire? Is someone you know sick?
Well, yeah, I guess you could say that.
I understand. We have many students who have enrolled to research cures and the like for their loved ones.
A noble pursuit.
Okay, so what exactly would you like me to do?
I understand that you've mastered spellcasting without incantations.
I would like for you to demonstrate.
I've arranged for our resident silentcaster to help us verify your abilities.
One of our brightest students. This is Fitz.
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you. I'm Rudeus Greyrat.
Provided this goes well, I'll be your underclassman this coming semester.
And if you find me lacking in any way, I hope you'll help guide me along.
Um, sure. I'm Fitz. Pleasure.
Your test today will be a mock duel. With primarily voiceless magic, if you please.
Yes, sir.
Wait. If I lose, is he gonna make me pay tuition?
That would suck. I don't want to do that.
Cute wand.
Now, begin!
Really? But how?
Good question.
No wonder.
I have to know.
How did you do that?
That was just a disturbed magic spell.
Do you not know it?
Aw, man.
Did I just publicly embarrass an upperclassman?
Thank you for going so easy on me.
You didn't have to let me win just because I'm new here, but I do appreciate it.
Soft hands. He's probably never held a weapon.
Hey, I really do owe you one, so I'll find some way to pay you back for this soon.
And so, a month later, I was living in the university dorms.
I also got a better breakdown of what being a special student means.
We're exempt from paying tuition, and we're excused from most, if not all, regular lessons.
As long as I attend a homeroom meeting once a month, I can pretty much do whatever I want here.
We're treated more like research staff than regular students.
And we're obviously still ambassadors for the school when we're off campus.
But it's almost more freedom than I know what to do with.
Well, how do I look?
I bet you'd have an even easier time picking up guys around here if you shortened your skirt a little bit.
Just long enough to hide your underwear.
Yeah, I suppose I could, but what if I get too cold?
Then just wear stockings up to your thighs.
But of course, just what I'd expect from your brilliant intellect.
And now, a few words from the student council president.
Isn't that Princess Ariel?
It is. So that must be silent bits.
Oh, it's Master Luke.
My goodness, isn't that the same sweet little boy you brought to tears during your exhibition battle?
Don't say it like that. I didn't make him cry.
Silence! Princess Ariel wishes to speak.
Oh, he's pretty.
He kind of reminds me of Paul.
The floor is yours, Your Highness.
I am Aria Onomoi Asura.
I'm the second princess of the Asura Kingdom and leader of this university student council.
You have made the pilgrimage to the Rinoa University of Magic from around the world and all walks of life.
Our student body is made up of many different clans and races, from humans to demons and beast folk.
Language and cultural barriers between students may feel daunting.
However, you would do well to remember you mustn't persecute your fellow students, simply because their race or speech is different.
Let's all follow the rules, don't make anyone uncomfortable, all pretty standard initiation kind of stuff.
It would normally bore me, but she's got real charisma.
I just want to listen to her.
And finally, we welcome you with open arms and wish you pleasant and enriching lives here.
Crap!
I forgot to do something nice for that guy after the test.
Please don't hold that against me.
Uh, is this the special student class?
Master!
Tell me you haven't forgotten your student!
It is I, Zanuba!
Uh, nope, of course I remember you!
Please let go, my pupil, you're scaring me a little.
How are you, master?
Well, right now, I'm glad to find your highness and good-
No!
I don't like him, Meow.
Huh?
Meow?
But Mistress Lenia, this is the young man I was telling you about before.
My master-
Bring him here, Meow.
Uh, well-
Hang on, is he getting bullied?
I thought Zanuba was pretty strong, but can't deny what it looks like.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Rudeus Greyrat.
I'm honored to be joining your class.
Either way, acting humble is the way to go with people like her.
Then I can just avoid her as best I can.
Wow, I like that you know your place, Meow.
Name's Lenia de Doldia.
I'm a fifth year.
And my dad, Gaius, he's the warchief of Doldia Village, Meow.
So you had better watch your step.
I figured she was a Doldia.
But Gaius' daughter?
He did say his oldest was studying abroad.
I guess now I know where.
Memories.
Ah, blue.
It stinks in here.
Excuse me, we haven't been introduced yet either.
May I ask your name as well?
It's Persina.
My deal is the same as Lina's.
Persina, huh?
That's a really beautiful name.
Glad to meet you.
No need not know.
Uh.
Hey.
Yes?
Can I help you?
Just double-checking.
You said your name was Rudeus, that right?
Yes.
Rudeus Greyrat at your service.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
I'm Cliff Grimoire.
I'm a magical genius.
He calls himself a genius?
That's not embarrassing.
I'm a second year, but I've already achieved advanced rankings in all offensive magics.
As well as healing, detoxification, and divine magic.
I'm a beginner with barriers, but I'll be intermediate soon.
Wow, that's really impressive.
Don't be so effusive.
I know you're a mage, of course.
But you're a swordsman too, right?
Yes, though I only dabble nowadays.
But how do you know that?
Who told you that I was a swordsman?
Eris did.
Eris?
Is she enrolled here too?
Really?
No, of course she isn't.
Yeah, fair.
There's no way in hell Eris would go back to school now.
So, um, where exactly did you cross paths?
And now there's only one of us you haven't met yet.
Although, she may not come by at all.
So she doesn't attend classes?
Nope.
And as you can see, she's even exempt from our monthly homeroom meetings.
She spends the vast majority of her time in her research laboratory.
Well, in that case, whatever she's researching must be huge.
Oh, but of course she ventures outside when she needs to.
I'm sure you'll meet her eventually.
You want to hang out later?
I still have homework.
Well, the man god said if I want to get my mojo back, I need to investigate the displacement incident.
All right.
The man-god said if I want to get my mojo back, I need to investigate the displacement incident.
I can do that.
This library is gigantic.
But that kind of makes it difficult to start.
Please forgive me for the other day.
I was overzealous with my magic and caused you to lose face.
I intended to bring you a gift of some kind in repayment, but I haven't quite found the chance yet.
But the next time I see you, I-
It's fine.
And you don't have to bow.
Um, Rudeus, was it?
What brings you to the library?
Just a bit of research.
Oh? Into what?
The mass teleportation.
Really?
Why?
Well, I grew up in and around the Fatoa region of Asura myself, but the incident teleported me to the middle of the Demon Continent.
Demon Continent?
Yes. The journey home took just about three years.
My family all seems to have been found in that time, but as far as I know, one of my old friends is still missing.
And you came here to investigate where they might have wound up?
Yes, I did.
Yeah, let's stick with that instead of jumping straight to erectile dysfunction.
But I mean, I do want to learn more about the Mana disaster, too.
I see. You really are incredible.
I should be going. See you around, Rudeus.
Oh, yeah. See you.
Oh.
For your research, Rude Animus is exploring the teleporter labyrinth.
It is a narrative account, but it's a good place to start.
Thank you very much.
That was really kind, and he honestly doesn't seem to be holding a grudge after that mock battle.
Maybe the tough guy Shades threw me off, and he's actually a pretty great guy.
Oh. So your highness is here studying abroad?
Yes. And I practice my earth magic every day.
Is that so? Then once I'm settled, let's make a figure together.
Yes!
Oh, uh, should I address you as royalty or just an upperclassman?
Please, we needn't bother with titles at all, dear master.
Far be it for me to tell you what to do, but you are free to simply call me Zanoba.
Zanoba, then.
Master!
You. Aren't you Fitz's...
Nice to meet you. My name is Rudeus Greyrat.
It's my first day as a student here, so I'll be looking to you upperclassmen for guidance.
Yes, I'm aware. Fitz said as much. And that you're rather forgetful.
Forgetful? Me? What does he think I'm forgetting?
Anyway, you do know who I am, don't you?
No, actually, I'm afraid I don't, but if you would be so kind as to introduce yourself...
I shouldn't be surprised that I'm beneath your notice. Even so...
I think you misunderstand.
My name is Luke Notos Greyrat.
Notos Greyrat?
Notos is Paul's branch of the family, so I guess that makes him my cousin.
Hmph.
He comes from Asura nobility.
Although he is technically a student, his true purpose here is to act as a bodyguard for his liege princess Ariel, so...
She's the second princess of the Asura kingdom, isn't she? I wonder what brought her here.
I'm given to understand that she lost the struggle to become heir apparent to the throne and used her studies as a pretext to flee the country.
Now, Luke could have stayed in Asura and become a guardian knight to one of her siblings,
but I believe he enrolled here to stay by Ariel's side in the event she decides to return to her kingdom and reignite her bid for succession.
Her other bodyguard is Silent Fitz.
He's a skilled mage who doesn't use incantations, but that's all anybody knows about him.
And that he's an elf, I suppose.
Hmph.
I returned to wandering the library after lunch, but the sun was setting before I knew it.
If I want to do any real research, I'd better bring a notebook or something next time.
Hmph.
It's white, but it's not snow.
Oh.
It's panties.
Hmph.
Excuse me, you dropped these?
Ah!
Underwear thief!
Huh?
Hmph!
Ah!
Hey, look!
I, uh...
Degenerate filth.
Please withhold judgment.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Oh?
You haven't?
Then explain what you've got in your hat.
Those are Princess Ariel's undergarments.
You may idolize her highness, but you may not rob her.
Shame!
Tell him!
You freak!
Die!
Get over here, pipsqueak!
Maybe I should shatter your arms so you never try this again.
Ah, wait!
Stop!
My apologies!
It's on me.
I dropped those when I was hanging them out to dry.
All he did was stop them touching the ground.
Hmph!
Even if that is true, we can't just let him off the hook when he start strolling
by the girls' dormitories after sundown.
Everyone knows male students are forbidden from using this pathway after hours.
I actually didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
You're right, pipsqueak!
Maybe I should shatter your arms so you never try this again.
Ah, wait!
Stop!
My apologies.
It's on me.
I dropped those when I was hanging them out to dry.
All he did was stop them touching the ground.
Hmph!
Even if that is true, we can't just let him off the hook when he's out strolling by the girls' dormitories after sundown.
Everyone knows male students are forbidden from using this pathway after hours.
I actually didn't know that.
He's a new student and he's not familiar with the more intricate dorm rules yet.
Let the infraction go.
If Silent Fitz vouches for him, there must be something redeemable about this boy.
Unfortunately for him, that's beside the point.
The rules have been violated, and an example must be made.
He will be ba-
I'm telling you he did nothing wrong.
So take your hands off him.
M-Master Fitz?
Unless you would all prefer a trip to the infirmary, then release him now.
M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M!
Yeah, fine. Whatever you say, Fitz.
But next time I won't be so nice!
Ugh, sorry about that. Goliad can be difficult to reason with sometimes.
I'm so sorry. You only got in trouble because I was careless with the laundry.
Oh, gosh, no. That wasn't your fault at all. But thanks for your help. I don't know what would have happened if you hadn't been there.
Don't mention it. Anybody would have done the same thing. Doesn't seem that way to me. He's been so impartial. And kind. What a great guy.
Master?
Yeah. That feels right. He deserves the utmost respect. Master Fitz, I'm truly grateful for your help.
I don't know what would have happened if you hadn't been there.
Don't mention it. Anybody would have done the same thing.
Doesn't seem that way to me. He's been so impartial. And kind. What a great guy.
Master?
Yeah. That feels right. He deserves the utmost respect.
I don't know if I can get used to you thanking me. It feels a little odd.
Oh, really? Like, what's so odd about it?
Can't say.
Hm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
I don't know, you, I don't know.
They love for you.
Oh.
Please, please.
Um.
La-ya-la-ya-la